http://www.sealmaster.net/privacy-policy

MenuAsphalt SealcoatingAsphalt & Pothole RepairCrack Filling & SealingParking Lot StripingColored PavementFAQHow Much Does it Cost to Stripe a Parking Lot?How to Apply Hot Rubberized Crack SealantsWhat is Hot Rubberized Crack Sealant?How to Repair Cracks in Asphalt PavementHow much does asphalt crack filling cost?How to fix a potholeHow much does it cost to fix a pothole?How often should you sealcoat a parking lot or driveway?How to sealcoat a parking lot or drivewayHow Much Does it Cost to Sealcoat a Parking Lot or Driveway?How to Color Asphalt PavementPrivacy & Personal Data Protection PolicySealMaster respects the privacy and confidentiality of individuals who visit the SealMaster website located at www.sealmaster.net. SealMaster maintains this Privacy Policy to help you understand the commitment to safeguard the privacy of the information you provide. This Privacy Policy outlines the information which SealMaster will collect from you and how that information will be used.Information Collection and UseIt is the policy of SealMaster not to sell, share, transfer, or rent to third parties any information you provide to SealMaster, through the use of the SealMaster website, without your written consent except as required by the credit application process, operation of the law or in compliance with legal authorities. SealMaster collects information about visitors, users and any other individual connecting to the SealMaster website. The information gathered and stored includes contact names, telephone numbers, fax numbers, addresses, email address, passwords and any other related data gathered while visiting the SealMaster website..SealMaster collects personal data only through inquiries, registration or other voluntary means.Personal information SealMaster collects is not distributed to third parties, other than to finance companies when credit is requested, and is reported in aggregate only. SealMaster routinely collects, compiles, and reports statistics and information reflecting the use of the SealMaster website in order to improve and/or expedite marketing and promotional efforts, analyze SealMaster website usage, improve SealMaster website content and layout and generate aggregate reports on trends, interests and behavior.Password ControlVisitors and users of SealMaster’s website are required to control the security of their password. SealMaster is not responsible for any damages arising out of the loss or misuse of passwords. Note that SealMaster will never ask for your password in an unsolicited phone call or e-mail.Accuracy of DataWhile SealMaster uses reasonable efforts to include accurate and up-to-date information in the website, SealMaster makes no warranties or representations as to its accuracy. SealMaster assumes no liability or responsibility for any errors or omissions in the content of the website.Third Party WebsitesThe SealMaster website may contain links to other websites. SealMaster is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other web websites. Customers and visitors are responsible for reviewing third party privacy statements to understand their policies. Customers and visitors who access a linked website may be disclosing their private information. It is the responsibility of the user to keep such information private and confidential.Changes to SealMaster’s Privacy PolicySealMaster reserves the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Notification regarding significant changes in the way SealMaster treats personal data will be sent by notice either in an email or by placing any changes on the SealMaster website.Questions and SuggestionsQuestions or suggestions regarding SealMaster’s Privacy & Personal Data Protection Policy should be directed to SealMaster by phoning 800-326-1994.SELECT YOUR AREASealcoating ContractorProperty ManagerRoad MaintenanceSport SurfacingArchitect/EngineerFranchise Opportunity LOCATIONSLocate InstallersContact a Location FRANCHISE LOGINVIEW PARTS ONLINE PRODUCTS & SERVICESPavement SealersSealer AdditivesCrack FillersPreparation & RepairTraffic PaintsConcrete ProductsDust SuppressantEquipmentTools & AccessoriesSport SurfacingPartsMerchandise RESOURCESInformation LibraryProduct Technical Data (TDS)Engineering SpecsCertificatesMSDSEquipment MaintenanceCredit ApplicationSealcoat Material CalculatorTank Volume CalculatorBrochures & Catalogs MEDIAVideo COMPANYContact UsCareersNewsBlogFacebookTwitterInstagramYouTubeLinkedInPrivacy Policy
Scroll to topENES
